http://www.diversgifts.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes how and when we collect, use, and share information when you purchase an item from us, contact us, or otherwise use our services through Shopify or its related sites and services.Information I Collect: To fulfil your order, you must provide us with certain information (which you authorised Shopify to provide to us), such as your name, email address, postal address, payment information, and the details of the product that you’re ordering. You may also choose to provide us with additional personal information (for a custom order of jewellery, for example), if you contact us directly.Why We Need Your Information and How We Use It:
as needed to provide our services, such as when we use your information to fulfil your order, to answer queries, or to provide customer support
as necessary for the purpose of our legitimate interests, if those legitimate interests are not overridden by your rights or interests, such as 1) providing and improving our services. We use your information to provide the services you requested and in our legitimate interest to improve our services; and 2) Compliance with the Shopify Seller Policy and Terms of Use. We use your information as necessary to comply with our obligations under the Shopify Seller Policy and Terms of Use.
Information Sharing and Disclosure:Information about our customers is important to our business. We share your personal information for very limited reasons and in limited circumstances. Specifically, we share information with Shopify as necessary to provide you our services and comply with our obligations under both the Shopify Seller Policy and Shopify Terms of Use.Data Retention:We retain your personal information only for as long as necessary to provide you with our services and as described in our Privacy Policy. However, we may also be required to retain this information to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations, to resolve disputes, and to enforce our agreements. Your Rights:
You may have the right to access and receive a copy of the personal information we hold about you by contacting us using the contact information below.
You may also have rights to change, restrict our use of, or delete your personal information. Absent exceptional circumstances (like where we are required to store data for legal reasons) we will generally delete your personal information upon request.
How to Contact Us:For purposes of EU data protection law, we, Divers Gifts & Collectables are the data controller of your personal information. If you have any questions or concerns, you may contact us at:sales@diversgifts.com
